http://www.thebeadgallery.com/pages/cookie-policy

HomeTBG Exclusives!Kits/Mixes Bead MixesJewelry KitsMask Leash KitsGemstones By the PieceStrandsGem PalettesTumbled Gems & RocksGemstone MeaningsBeads WoodSeed BeadsArtist Made GlassSwarovski CrystalGlassSupplies Mask Leash SuppliesCharms and PendantsFindingsCords and ChainsToolsJewelry BraceletsNecklacesEarringsRingsCustomer Care Current Events Past EventsCOVID-19 UpdateFrequently Asked QuestionsShippingHappiness GuaranteeLegal and Policies Privacy PolicyTerms of ServiceRefund policyCookie PolicyAbout UsFind Us Private Appointment
Skip to content
COOKIE POLICY
Last updated November 24, 2019
This Cookie Policy explains how The Bead Gallery ("Company", "we", "us", and "our") uses cookies and similar technologies to recognize you when you visit our websites at https://thebeadgallery.com, ("Websites"). It explains what these technologies are and why we use them, as well as your rights to control our use of them.
In some cases we may use cookies to collect personal information, or that becomes personal information if we combine it with other information.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small data files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.
Cookies set by the website owner (in this case, The Bead Gallery) are called "first party cookies". Cookies set by parties other than the website owner are called "third party cookies". Third party cookies enable third party features or functionality to be provided on or through the website (e.g. like advertising, interactive content and analytics). The parties that set these third party cookies can recognize your computer both when it visits the website in question and also when it visits certain other websites.
Why do we use cookies?
We use first and third party cookies for several reasons. Some cookies are required for technical reasons in order for our Websites to operate, and we refer to these as "essential" or "strictly necessary" cookies. Other cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our Online Properties. Third parties serve cookies through our Websites for advertising, analytics and other purposes. This is described in more detail below.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
How can I control cookies?
You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies. You can exercise your cookie rights by setting your preferences in the Cookie Consent Manager. The Cookie Consent Manager allows you to select which categories of cookies you accept or reject. Essential cookies cannot be rejected as they are strictly necessary to provide you with services.
The Cookie Consent Manager can be found in the notification banner and on our website. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. You may also set or amend your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser's help menu for more information.
In addition, most advertising networks offer you a way to opt out of targeted advertising. If you would like to find out more information, please visit http://www.aboutads.info/choices/ or http://www.youronlinechoices.com.
The specific types of first and third party cookies served through our Websites and the purposes they perform are described in the table below (please note that the specific cookies served may vary depending on the specific Online Properties you visit):
Essential website cookies:
These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our Websites and to use some of its features, such as access to secure areas.
Name:
__tlbcpv
Purpose:
Used to record the cookie consent preferences of visitors
Provider:
.termly.io
Service:
Termly View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
20 years
Name:
__tltpl_#
Purpose:
Used to record the policies that visitors consent to
Provider:
.termly.io
Service:
Termly View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
20 years
Name:
__tluid
Purpose:
Assigns a random ID number to each visitor so that their policy consent and cookie consent preferences can be saved.
Provider:
.termly.io
Service:
Termly View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
20 years
Name:
__cfduid
Purpose:
Used by Cloudflare to identify individual clients behind a shared IP address, and apply security settings on a per-client basis. This is a HTTP type cookie that expires after 1 year.
Provider:
.thebeadgallery.com
Service:
CloudFlare View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 month
Analytics and customization cookies:
These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our Websites are being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our Websites for you.
Name:
_gat#
Purpose:
Enables Google Analytics regulate the rate of requesting. It is a HTTP cookie type that lasts for a session.
Provider:
.thebeadgallery.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 minute
Name:
_gid
Purpose:
Keeps an entry of unique ID which is then used to come up with statistical data on website usage by visitors. It is a HTTP cookie type and expires after a browsing session.
Provider:
.thebeadgallery.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 day
Name:
#collect
Purpose:
Sends data such as visitor’s behavior and device to Google Analytics. It is able to keep track of the visitor across marketing channels and devices. It is a pixel tracker type cookie whose activity lasts within the browsing session.
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
United States
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
session
Name:
_ga
Purpose:
It records a particular ID used to come up with data about website usage by the user. It is a HTTP cookie that expires after 2 years.
Provider:
.thebeadgallery.com
Service:
Google Analytics View Service Privacy Policy
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 12 months 4 days
Unclassified cookies:
These are cookies that have not yet been categorized. We are in the process of classifying these cookies with the help of their providers.
Name:
_s
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
30 minutes
Name:
cart_sig
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
14 days
Name:
_y
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 11 months 24 days
Name:
_shopify_fs
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 11 months 24 days
Name:
_orig_referrer
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
14 days
Name:
_shopify_country
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
session
Name:
_shopify_y
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
server_cookie
Expires in:
1 year 12 months 5 days
Name:
secure_customer_sig
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
20 years
Name:
_landing_page
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
14 days
Name:
_shopify_sa_t
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
30 minutes
Name:
_shopify_s
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
30 minutes
Name:
_shopify_sa_p
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
30 minutes
Name:
cart_currency
Purpose:
__________
Provider:
thebeadgallery.com
Service:
__________
Country:
Canada
Type:
http_cookie
Expires in:
14 days
What about other tracking technologies, like web beacons?
Cookies are not the only way to recognize or track visitors to a website. We may use other, similar technologies from time to time, like web beacons (sometimes called "tracking pixels" or "clear gifs"). These are tiny graphics files that contain a unique identifier that enable us to recognize when someone has visited our Websites or opened an e-mail including them. This allows us, for example, to monitor the traffic patterns of users from one page within a website to another, to deliver or communicate with cookies, to understand whether you have come to the website from an online advertisement displayed on a third-party website, to improve site performance, and to measure the success of e-mail marketing campaigns. In many instances, these technologies are reliant on cookies to function properly, and so declining cookies will impair their functioning.
Do you use Flash cookies or Local Shared Objects?
Websites may also use so-called "Flash Cookies" (also known as Local Shared Objects or "LSOs") to, among other things, collect and store information about your use of our services, fraud prevention and for other site operations.
Do you serve targeted advertising?
Third parties may serve cookies on your computer or mobile device to serve advertising through our Websites. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. They may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of advertisements. This can be accomplished by them using cookies or web beacons to collect information about your visits to this and other sites in order to provide relevant advertisements about goods and services of potential interest to you. The information collected through this process does not enable us or them to identify your name, contact details or other details that directly identify you unless you choose to provide these.
How often will you update this Cookie Policy?
We may update this Cookie Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to the cookies we use or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. Please therefore re-visit this Cookie Policy regularly to stay informed about our use of cookies and related technologies.
The date at the top of this Cookie Policy indicates when it was last updated.
Where can I get further information?
If you have any questions about our use of cookies or other technologies, please email us at info@thebeadgallery.com.
Added to your cart:
(-)
Cart subtotal
